var qnbank = [{
  sno: 1,
  question: 'What is the opposite of father?',
  options: ['Sister', 'Auntie', 'Mother', 'Uncle'],
  answer: 2
},
  {
    sno: 2,
    question: 'What is 1 + 2 ?',
    options: ['2', '3', '6', '12'],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    sno: 3,
    question: 'What is 2 + 3 ?',
    options: ['2', '3', '6', '5'],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    sno: 4,
    question: 'What is 3 + 4 ?',
    options: ['7', '3', '6', '12'],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    sno: 5,
    question: 'What is 4 + 5 ?',
    options: ['9', '3', '6', '12'],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    sno: 6,
    question: 'What is 5 + 6 ?',
    options: ['2', '3', '6', '11'],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    sno: 7,
    question: 'What is 6 + 7 ?',
    options: ['2', '3', '13', '12'],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    sno: 8,
    question: 'What is 7 + 8 ?',
    options: ['2', '15', '6', '12'],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    sno: 9,
    question: 'What is 8 + 9 ?',
    options: ['2', '17', '6', '12'],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    sno: 10,
    question: 'What is 9 + 10 ?',
    options: ['2', '3', '19', '12'],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    sno: 11,
    question: 'What is 10 + 11 ?',
    options: ['2', '3', '21', '12'],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    sno: 12,
    question: 'What is 11 + 12 ?',
    options: ['2', '23', '6', '12'],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    sno: 13,
    question: 'What is 12 + 13 ?',
    options: ['25', '3', '6', '12'],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    sno: 14,
    question: 'What is 13 + 14 ?',
    options: ['27', '3', '6', '12'],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    sno: 15,
    question: 'What is 14 + 15 ?',
    options: ['2', '3', '29', '12'],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    sno: 16,
    question: 'What is 15 + 16 ?',
    options: ['2', '31', '6', '12'],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    sno: 17,
    question: 'What is 16 + 17 ?',
    options: ['33', '3', '6', '12'],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    sno: 18,
    question: 'What is 17 + 18 ?',
    options: ['2', '3', '6', '35'],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    sno: 19,
    question: 'What is 18 + 19 ?',
    options: ['2', '3', '6', '37'],
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    sno: 20,
    question: 'What is 19 + 20 ?',
    options: ['2', '39', '6', '12'],
    answer: 1
  }
  ]

// var paragraph = document.createElement('p')
// paragraph.textContent = '... blablabla ...'
// document.body.appendChild(paragraph)

// var pDiv = document.getElementById("paragraphs");

// Create a new div if not exist
// if (!pDiv) {
//              pDiv = document.createElement("div");
//              pDiv.id = "paragraphs";
//              pDiv.innerHTML = "<p>Paragraph 1</p>";
//              document.body.appendChild(pDiv);
//            }
//
//            var p = document.createElement("p");
//            var t = document.createTextNode(<p>Paragraph 2</p>);
//            p.appendChild(t);
//            pDiv.appendChild(p);
